<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Read on Zhanbo&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>/posts/read/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Read on Zhanbo&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 00:36:57 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/read/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Zyzzyva: Speculative Byzantine Fault Tolerance</title>
      <link>/posts/read/zyzzyva/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 00:36:57 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/read/zyzzyva/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Zyzzyva是一种使用投机来降低成本并简化拜占庭容错状态机复制设计的协议。在 Zyzzyva 中，副本响应客户端的请求，而无需首先运行昂贵的三阶段提交协</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ByzantizingPaxos</title>
      <link>/posts/read/byzantizingpaxos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 00:49:48 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/read/byzantizingpaxos/</guid>
      <description>之前对于Byzantine Paxos的理解完全建立在Youtube上Mu Shuai老师的讲解视频上，现在决定好好读一遍Lamport老爷爷的</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monoxide: Scale out Blockchains with Asynchronous Consensus Zones</title>
      <link>/posts/read/monoxide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 01:01:06 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/read/monoxide/</guid>
      <description>Problem In general blockchain, every single node is required to replicate, validate, store and maintain the states of all users in entire network. Solution This paper present a idea to divide the blockchain into different asynchronous consensus zones (multi-instanitiation of independent blockchain systems). Partitioning workloads of the entire network, distribute to zones. Parallelize blovk creation and transaction handling since we have multi-independent blockchain. To achieve linear scalability as the entire</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Towards Scaling Blockchain Systems via Sharding</title>
      <link>/posts/read/sharding1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 01:01:06 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/read/sharding1/</guid>
      <description>Abstract &amp;ldquo;Scaling blockchain systems under general workloads remains an open question&amp;rdquo;. The challenges of scaling are different between databasebases and blockchain since they have different failure models. The major contribution of this paper: Enhance the performance of Byzantine consensus protocols -&amp;gt; inprove the individual shard&amp;rsquo;s throughput. Design an efficient shard formation protocol -&amp;gt; leverage a trsted random beacon to securely assign nodes into shards. Design a general distributed transaction protocol</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
